Luyu Yang

RESEARCH INTEREST My research currently lies at the intersection of computer vision and machine learning. I develop learning algorithms which facilitate the transfer of information through unsupervised and semi-supervised model adaptation, through which my work enables systems to tackle real-world variations and minimizes human supervision. Before this, I have also worked on activity recognition in videos.

EDUCATION

University of Maryland,

Aug 2018 – Present

PhD, Computer Science

Advised by Abhinav Shrivastava and Larry Davis

Chongqing University of Posts and Telecommunications,

Sep 2008 – Jul 2015

B.S. and M.S., Electrical and Telecommunication Engineering

Graduated with Honors

APPOINTMENTS

Salesforce Research

Jun 2021 – Aug 2021

Research Intern

Facebook AI

Oct 2019 – May 2020

Research Intern

Cornell University

Feb 2018 – Jun 2018

Research Assistant of Kilian Q. Weinberger

PUBLICATIONS AND PRE-PRINTS

- [1] **Luyu Yang**, Mingfei Gao, Zeyuan Chen, Ran Xu, Abhinav Shrivastava, Chetan Ramaiah, "Burn After Reading: Online Adaptation for Cross-domain Streaming Data," *Under review*, March 2022
- [2] Shuaiyi Huang, **Luyu Yang**, Bo He, Songyang Zhang, Xuming He, Abhinav Shrivastava, "Learning Semantic Correspondence with Sparse Annotations," *Under review*, March 2022
- [3] Yu Shen, **Luyu Yang**, Xijun Wang, Abhinav Shrivastava, Ming Lin, "Lessons from Multi-modality Teachers for Autonomous Driving," *Under review*, March 2022
- [4] **Luyu Yang**, Yan Wang, Mingfei Gao, Abhinav Shrivastava, Kilian Q. Weinberger, Wei-lun Chao, Ser-Nam Lim, "Deep Co-training with Task Decomposition for Semi-supervised Domain Adaptation," **ICCV**, 2021
- [5] **Luyu Yang**, Yogesh Balaji, Ser-Nam Lim, Abhinav Shrivastava, "Curriculum Manager for Source Selection in Multi-source Domain Adaptation," *ECCV*, 2020
- [6] Lan Wang, Chenqiang Gao, **Luyu Yang**, Yue Zhao, Wangmeng Zuo, Deyu Meng, "PM-GANs: Discriminative Representation Learning for Action Recognition Using Partial-modalities," *ECCV*, 2018
- [7] **Luyu Yang**, Jack Z.G. Tan, Zhe Huang, Gene Cheung, "A Content-aware Metric for Stitched Panoramic Image Quality Assessment," *ICCV workshop on MVR3D*, 2017
- [8] **Luyu Yang**, Jiang Liu, Chenqiang Gao, "An Error-activation-guided Blind Metric for Stitched Panoramic Image Quality Assessment," *CCF Chinese Conference on Computer Vision*, 2017
- [9] Chenqiang Gao, **Luyu Yang**, Yinhe Du, Zeming Feng, Jiang Liu, "From constrained to unconstrained datasets: an evaluation of local action descriptors and fusion strategies for interaction recognition," *World Wide Web*, 2016
- [10] **Luyu Yang**, Chenqiang Gao, Deyu Meng, Lu Jiang, "A Novel Group-Sparsity-Optimization-Based Feature Selection Model for Complex Interaction Recognition," *ACCV*, 2014
- [11] Chenqiang Gao, Yinhe Du, Jiang Liu, **Luyu Yang**, Deyu Meng, "A New Dataset and Evaluation for Infrared Action Recognition," *CCF Chinese Conference on Computer Vision*, 2015 (*Best paper nominee*)

AWARDS AND HONORS Nominee of Google PhD Fellowship, only 1 in the department2021Dean's Fellowship, University of Maryland, Computer Science2018 – 2019All-star Employee Award, Tencent Technology, 5% employee2016 – 2017The Principal's Honor Award, CQUPT2012

CONTACT

E-mail: loyo@umd.edu Website: http://www.loyo.me/